<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RunForLove</string>
    <string name="connexion">Connection</string>
    <string name="inscription">Register</string>
    <string name="slogan">Cross new borders</string>
    <string name="bienvenue">Welcome among us</string>
    <string name="notifConnexion">Nice to see you again</string>
    <string name="notifDeco">See you soon</string>
    <string name="notifModif">A new ID for a new life</string>
    <string name="notifNDiscussion">Let\'s talk to</string>
    <string name="notifNActivite">You ran</string>
    <string name="notifNEvent">has been created</string>
    <string name="enfj">" Protagonist"</string>
    <string name="annuler">Cancel</string>
    <string name="ajouter">Add</string>
    <string name="ajouterPersonne">Add someone</string>
    <string name="certain">Do you really want to delete this conversation?</string>
    <string name="ajouterEvent">" Schedule other meetings"</string>
    <string name="ajouterActivite">" Nothing to report?"</string>
    <string name="utilisateurAjoute">User has been added</string>
    <string name="utilisateurNon">This user does not exist</string>
    <string name="pseudoDestinnataire">" The receiver"</string>
    <string name="conversationExist">A conversation has this name</string>
    <string name="creerUneDiscussion">Create a new conversation</string>
    <string name="creerDiscussion">Create</string>
    <string name="mesConversations">My conversations</string>
    <string name="nouvelleConversation">+ Send a message to new people +</string>
    <string name="datePasValide">The correct format date is yyyy/MM/dd and it cannot be in the future</string>
    <string name="pasMiens">You do not have event</string>
    <string name="eventMiens">My events</string>
    <string name="pasProchain">No event soon</string>
    <string name="eventProchains">Next events</string>
    <string name="supprimerEvent">Delete an event</string>
    <string name="pasVille">No event soon in your city</string>
    <string name="eventDansVille">Next events in your city</string>
    <string name="eventAEteCrees">The event has been created</string>
    <string name="eventExist">This event exists</string>
    <string name="creer">Create an event</string>
    <string name="dateEvent">Date of the event</string>
    <string name="villeEvent">City of the event</string>
    <string name="aVenir">Events to come</string>
    <string name="dansVille">Events in your city</string>
    <string name="mesEvents">My events</string>
    <string name="nouvelEvent">+ Add a new event +</string>
    <string name="parcouru">You ran</string>
    <string name="activiteCree">The activity has been created</string>
    <string name="etreUn">"You are a "</string>
    <string name="supprimer">Delete the activity</string>
    <string name="same">" A record already has this name"</string>
    <string name="enregistrer">Rgister</string>
    <string name="distance">Distance in km:</string>
    <string name="minutes">Minutes:</string>
    <string name="heures">Hours:</string>
    <string name="infos">" Further information"</string>
    <string name="nom">Give a name</string>
    <string name="mesActivites">My activities</string>
    <string name="nouvelleActivite">+ Add a new activity +</string>
    <string name="echec_modifierAge">" You must be over 18"</string>
    <string name="echec_modifierMDP">" Passwords must be identical and not empty"</string>
    <string name="deconnexion">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="modifier">Modifie my profile</string>
    <string name="echec_authentification">" Authentication failed"</string>
    <string name="pasPersonnalite">" Come discover your personality"</string>
    <string name="pasDiscussion">" Come talk to new people"</string>
    <string name="pasActivite">" You have not yet registered any activity"</string>
    <string name="event">" You have not yet participated in an event"</string>
    <string name="identifiantsIncorrects">Incorrect logins</string>
    <string name="pseudo_utilise">This psudo is used</string>
    <string name="ville">Your city</string>
    <string name="femme">Woman</string>
    <string name="homme">Man</string>
    <string name="age_faux">" Please enter your year of birth"</string>
    <string name="age_minimal">" You must be 18 years old"</string>
    <string name="saisir_dateNaissance">Year of birth</string>
    <string name="mdp_non_identique">Passwords are not the same</string>
    <string name="confirmer_mdp">Validate</string>
    <string name="saisir_mdp">Password</string>
    <string name="saisir_pseudo">Pseudo</string>
    <string name="champ_vide">" Please complete all fields"</string>
    <string name="s_inscrire">Register</string>
    <string name="se_connecter">Log in</string>
    <string name="mdp">Password</string>
    <string name="pseudo">" Username"</string>
    <string name="non">No</string>
    <string name="oui">Yes</string>
    <string name="test">Test of personnality \n Question</string>
    <string name="q15">At work and at home, your living environment is fairly orderly.</string>
    <string name="q14">Your dreams tend to focus on the real world and its events.</string>
    <string name="q13">You often justify yourself to your peers.</string>
    <string name="q12">" You prefer a social evening to a book or a video game"</string>
    <string name="q11">" You think to be an organized person."</string>
    <string name="q10">" As a parent, you would rather see your child become intelligent than kind."</string>
    <string name="q9">" You feel superior to others."</string>
    <string name="q8">" You don't mind being the center of attention."</string>
    <string name="q7">You try to reply to your emails as soon as possible and can\'t stand having a poorly organized mailbox.</string>
    <string name="q6">" You consider your mind more practical than creative."</string>
    <string name="q5">" You feel very anxious in stressful situations."</string>
    <string name="q4">" Usually you start the conversations."</string>
    <string name="q3">" You are not often lost in thought."</string>
    <string name="q2">" You rarely act by curiosity."</string>
    <string name="q1">" You care too much about what people think."</string>
    <string name="q0">" It’s easy for you to introduce yourself to others"</string>
    <string name="abrege_istp">" Bold and pragmatic experimenters, masters of all kinds of tools."</string>
    <string name="istp">" Virtuoso"</string>
    <string name="abrege_istj">" Pragmatic individuals interested in the facts, the seriousness of which cannot be questioned."</string>
    <string name="istj">" Logistician"</string>
    <string name="abrege_isfp">" Flexible and charming artists, always ready to explore and try something new."</string>
    <string name="isfp">" Adventurer"</string>
    <string name="abrege_isfj">" Very strong and very warm protectors, always ready to defend those they love."</string>
    <string name="isfj">" Defender"</string>
    <string name="abrege_intp">" Innovative inventors with an unquenchable thirst for knowledge."</string>
    <string name="intp">" Logician"</string>
    <string name="abrege_intj">" Imaginative thinkers and strategists, with a plan for everything."</string>
    <string name="intj">" Architect"</string>
    <string name="abrege_infp">" Poetic, kind and altruistic people who are always ready to support a good cause."</string>
    <string name="infp">" Mediator"</string>
    <string name="abrege_infj">" Calm and mystical idealists and yet very inspiring and tireless."</string>
    <string name="infj">" Lawyer"</string>
    <string name="inconnu">" You have not yet completed the personality test"</string>
    <string name="abrege_estp">" Clever, energetic and very perceptive people, who really like to live at the cutting edge of progress."</string>
    <string name="estp">" Contractor"</string>
    <string name="abrege_estj">" Excellent managers, of unequaled efficiency when it comes to managing things, or people."</string>
    <string name="estj">" Director"</string>
    <string name="abrege_esfp">" Spontaneous, energetic and enthusiastic entertainers; you never get bored with them."</string>
    <string name="esfp">Entertainer</string>
    <string name="abrege_esfj">" Extraordinarily caring, sociable and popular people, always ready to help others."</string>
    <string name="esfj">" Consul"</string>
    <string name="abrege_entp">" Clever and curious thinkers unable to resist an intellectual challenge."</string>
    <string name="entp">" Innovator"</string>
    <string name="abrege_entj">" Bold, imaginative and strong leaders, who always find a way to achieve their goals, or create it."</string>
    <string name="entj">Officer</string>
    <string name="abrege_enfp">" Enthusiastic, creative and sociable free spirits, who always find a reason to smile."</string>
    <string name="enfp">" Inspirator"</string>
    <string name="abrege_enfj">Charismatic and inspiring leaders, able to fascinate their audience.</string>
    <string name="description_enfj">The Protagonists are born leaders, plains of passion and charisma. They make up about two percent of the population and are often our politicians, coaches and teachers. They reach out to others and inspire them so that they are not satisfied and do good in the world. With a natural confidence that has aroused influence, the Protagonists take great pride and joy in helping others work together to improve themselves and their community.\n\nPeople are attracted to strong personalities and the Protagonists exude authenticity, concern and altruism. They are not afraid to stand up and speak up when they feel there is something to say. They find it natural and easy to communicate with others, especially directly, and their intuition helps people of \"Protagonist\" personality to touch everyone, whether through fact and logic or pure emotion. . Protagonists easily spot people\'s motives and seemingly disconnected events, and are able to collect these ideas and communicate them as a common goal with simply fascinating eloquence.\n\nPeople with \"Protagonist\" personalities are passionate altruists, sometimes even too much, and it is unlikely that they are afraid to take up arms to defend the people and the ideas in which they believe. It is not surprising that many of the famous protagonists are presidents of the USA because this type of personality wants to show the way towards a brighter future, whether by leading a nation to prosperity or by bringing a victory. bitterly contested for their little softball championship team.</string>
    <string name="description_enfp">The “Inspirator” personality is a true free spirit. They are often the soul of an evening but, unlike Explorers, they are less interested in the excitement and pure pleasure of the present moment than in appreciating the social and emotional connections they establish with others. Charming, independent, energetic and compassionate, the 7% of the population they represent can certainly be found in any crowd.\n\n That said, Inspirators are not just sociable seducers. They tend to think of life as a big complex puzzle where everything is connected, but, unlike Analysts, who tend to approach this puzzle as a series of systemic machinations, the Inspirators approach it through a prism emotional, compassionate and mystical, and they\'re always looking for an underlying meaning.\n\n Fortunately, Inspirateurs know how to relax and the passionate and motivated idealist of the workplace is perfectly capable of transforming into a free, imaginative and enthusiastic spirit on the dance floor, often with a suddenness that can surprise even his friends. the closest. Being in the know also gives them a chance to connect with others emotionally, to provide them with valuable insights into what motivates their friends and colleagues. They believe that everyone should take the time to recognize and express their feelings, and their empathy and sociability make this belief a natural topic of conversation.\n\n However, the “Inspiring” personality type must be careful: if he trusts his intuition too much, supposes or anticipates too much about a friend\'s motivations, he can misinterpret the signals and frustrate projects that a more direct approach would have simplified. This kind of social stress is the bane that sleeps the Diplomats, whose harmony is the main concern. Inspirators are very emotional and very sensitive, and when they offend someone, they feel it. Inspirators spend a lot of time exploring social relationships, feelings and ideas before finding something that seems truly authentic to them. However, when they finally find their place in this world, their imagination, empathy and courage are likely to produce surprising results.</string>
    <string name="description_entj">Commanders are born leaders. People with this personality type embody the gifts of charisma and confidence, and emanate from authority in a way that brings crowds together under the umbrella of a common goal. However, unlike their more sentimental counterparts, Commanders are characterized by an often relentless level of rationality. They use their drive, determination and quick wit to accomplish whatever goal they have set for themselves. They make up only three percent of the population and that may be a good thing because, otherwise, they could overpower the more shy and sensitive personality types that make up much of the rest of the world; that said, we must thank the Commanders for creating many of the businesses and institutions that we take for granted every day.\n\n If there is one thing the Commanders love, it is a good challenge, big or small, and they firmly believe that, if given enough time and resources, they can do anything. This quality makes people with a “Commander” personality type brilliant entrepreneurs, and their ability to think strategically and focus on a long-term goal while executing each step of their plan with determination and precision. made of powerful business leaders. This determination is often a self-fulfilling prophecy, as Commanders follow through on their intentions by sheer force of their will, while others give up and move on, and their Extroverted nature makes them susceptible to train everyone else with them and achieve dramatic results in doing so.\n\n The expression of emotions is not the strong point of Analysts, but the distance that Commanders leave between themselves and their emotions is essentially public and directly felt by a much wider range of people. Commanders tend to simply offend the sensitivity of those they consider ineffective, incompetent or lazy, especially in the professional environment. For people with a “Commander” personality type, showing your emotions is like showing your weakness, and it\'s easy to make enemies with this approach. Commanders would do well to remember that they absolutely need to have a functioning team, not only to achieve their goals but also to have good validation and good feedback, things to which, surprisingly, Commanders are very sensitive.\n\n Commanders are real batteries, maintain the image that they have of being larger than life, and they are quite often. However, they need to remember that their stature comes not only from their own actions but also from the actions of the team that supports them, and that it is important to recognize the contributions, talents and needs, especially of an emotional point of view, of their support network. Even if they have to adopt a \"pretend and the rest will follow\" mentality, if the Commanders manage to combine an emotionally healthy attention with their many strengths, they will be rewarded by deep and satisfying relationships and by all the stimulating victories. they can get.\n\n</string>
    <string name="description_entp">The \"Innovative\" personality type is the advocate of the ultimate devil who thrives on breaking down arguments and beliefs and letting the ripples flutter in the wind so that everyone can see them. Innovators don\'t do it because they\'re trying to reach a deeper goal or a strategic goal, but for the simple reason that it\'s fun. No one likes the mental wrestling process more than Innovators because it gives them the opportunity to exercise their beautiful fast and fluid mind, the large amount of knowledge they have accumulated and the ability to connect ideas together. disparate to prove they are right.\n\n As they take a certain pleasure in being part of the oppressed, the Innovators like the intellectual exercise which one finds in the questioning of the dominant mode of thought, which makes them irreplaceable when it is necessary to rework existing systems or to shake up certain things and make them go in nifty new directions. However, if they have to manage the day-to-day mechanics of actually implementing their suggestions, they will suffer. Innovators love to brainstorm and think big, but they will do anything to avoid having to do the \"dirty work.\" The Innovators represent only about three percent of the population, which is perfect, because it lets them create original ideas and then take a step back to let the more numerous and more meticulous personalities handle the logistical problems relating to the establishment and maintenance.\n\n Innovators find it harder than most people to exploit their natural abilities. Their intellectual independence and free-form vision are tremendously valuable when they are in power, or at least when they are listened to by someone in power, but getting to this point may require some level of follow-up that the Innovators have hard to supply.\n\n When they get a job like this, Innovators must remember that if they want their ideas to come to fruition, they will always need others to put the pieces together. If they have spent more time \"winning\" debates than building consensus, many Innovators will realize that they simply do not have enough support to succeed. By playing devil\'s advocate so well, people with this type of personality may find that the most complex and rewarding intellectual challenge is to understand a more sentimental point of view and to fight to defend the consideration and compromise along with logic and progress.</string>
    <string name="description_esfj">People who share the \"Consul\" personality type are popular for lack of a better term, which is logical, since it is also a very common personality type that represents twelve percent of the population. In high school, the Consuls are the majorettes and the quarterbacks, those who set the tone, capture the light of the spotlights and lead their team towards victory and fame. Later in their lives, Consuls still like to support their friends and loved ones, organize social gatherings and do their best to make sure everyone is happy.\n\n Consuls are selfless and take their responsibility to help others and do the right thing seriously. However, people who have the Consul personality type tend to base their moral principles on well-established traditions and laws and to uphold authority and rules rather than to choose philosophy or mysticism as the source. inspiration of their morals. That said, it is important for Consuls to remember that people come from many backgrounds and have many perspectives, so what may seem good to them is not always an absolute truth.\n\n In solidarity and extroverts, Consuls are always easy to spot in an evening: they are the ones who find the time to chat and laugh with everyone! However, their dedication is such that they don\'t just drop by and see you because they have to. Consuls really enjoy hearing about their friends\' relationships and activities, remember small details and are always ready to chat with human warmth and sensitivity. If something goes wrong or there is tension in the room, the Consuls come back to it and try to restore the harmony and stability of the group.\n\n Being very opposed to the concept of conflict, the Consuls devote a lot of their energy to establishing social order and prefer projects and organized events to endless activities planned or to small spontaneous parties. People with this personality type put a lot of effort into the activities they organize, and Consuls can easily feel hurt if their ideas are rejected or people are just not interested. Let us repeat: it is important that the Consuls do not forget that we all come from a different place and that the lack of interest is not a comment on them or on the activity that they organized but only a lack of hooked atoms.\n\n The most important challenge for Consuls is to come to terms with their sensitivity: it is inevitable that people will disagree or criticize and, even if it hurts, it is life. The best thing for Consuls to do is do what they do best: be a role model for others, take care of what they can take care of, and be happy that so many people actually appreciate the efforts that \'they do.</string>
    <string name="description_esfp">If a person is likely to start singing and dancing spontaneously, this is the \"Entertainer\" personality type. The Entertainers get carried away by the excitement of the present moment and want everyone else to feel the same way. No other personality type is as generous with their time and energy as the Entertainers when it comes to encouraging others, and no other personality type does it with such irresistible style.\n\n Born entertainers, Entertainers love being in the spotlight, but the world is a scene. Many famous people who have the “Entertainer” personality type are actually actors, but they just as much like to put on a show for their friends, to chat with a beautiful unique and earthy spirit, to attract attention and to give a festive air to every exit. Completely sociable, Entertainers like the simplest things and, for them, there is nothing more pleasant than having fun with a good group of friends.\n\n The biggest challenge that Entertainers face is that they are often so focused on the immediate pleasures that they neglect the duties and responsibilities that make these little luxuries possible. Complex analysis, repetitive tasks and comparing statistics with real consequences are not easy activities for Entertainers. They prefer to trust luck or opportunity, or simply ask for help from their large circle of friends. It is important that Entertainers challenge themselves in order to track long term things like their retirement plan or their sugar intake, as there will not always be someone else available to help them monitor these things.</string>
    <string name="description_estj">The Directors are the representatives of tradition and order. They use their understanding of what is right, wrong and socially acceptable to bring families and communities together. People with the \"Director\" personality type embrace the values ​​of honesty, dedication and dignity, are appreciated for the clarity of their advice and are happy to lead the way when the road is difficult. Directors are proud to bring people together. They often assume the role of community organizers and work hard to bring everyone together to celebrate local events that are dear to them or to defend traditional values ​​that keep families and communities together.\n\n The demand for this type of leadership is high in democratic countries and, since Directors make up no less than 11% of the population, it is not surprising that many American presidents have been Directors. The Directors firmly believe in the rule of law and the authority to be deserved, lead by example, demonstrate dedication and determined honesty, and absolutely reject laziness and dishonesty, especially at work. If there are people who say that hard manual labor is a great way to build character, it\'s the Directors.\n\n For Directors, the main challenge is to recognize that not everyone follows the same route or makes the same type of contribution. A true leader recognizes the strength of the individual as well as that of the group and helps to bring the ideas of these individuals to the table. In this way, the Directors really have all the facts and are able to lead the charge in directions that work for everyone.</string>
    <string name="description_istp">Virtuosos love exploring hands and eyes, touching and examining the world around them with calm rationalism and lively curiosity. People with this type of personality are born Maker who move from one project to another, build useful and superfluous things for fun and learn from their surroundings as they go. Often virtuosos and engineers, the greatest pleasure of Virtuosos is to get their hands dirty by taking things apart and putting them up a little better than they were before.\n\n Although their orientation towards mechanics might make it seem at first sight that they are simple people, Virtuosos are in fact quite mysterious. Friendly but very reserved, calm but suddenly spontaneous, extremely curious but unable to stay focused on conventional studies, people of \"Virtuoso\" personality can be difficult to predict, even by their friends and those they love. Virtuosos may sound very loyal and balanced for a time, but they tend to build up a supply of impulsive energy which explodes without warning and takes their centers of interest in intrepid new directions.\n\n Virtuosos come to learn that many other personality types have much sharper limits when it comes to acceptable rules and attitudes. They don’t want to hear an indelicate joke and they’re sure they wouldn’t tell anyone else, and they wouldn’t be rowdy, even with another willing person. If a situation is already emotionally charged, violating these limits can backfire sharply against the initiator.\n\n Virtuosos have a hard time predicting emotions, but this is just a natural extension of their honesty, given the difficulty in evaluating the virtuosos\' emotions and motivations. However, their tendency to explore relationships through action rather than empathy can lead to extremely frustrating situations. People with the Virtuoso personality type struggle with limits and guidelines. They prefer freedom of movement and color outside the lines if they feel the need.\n\n Finding an environment where they can work with good friends who understand their style and unpredictability by mixing their creativity with their sense of humor and their pragmatic approach to developing practical solutions and things will give Virtuosos a lot years of happiness during which they can build useful boxes and admire them from the outside.</string>
    <string name="description_istj">The “Logistician” personality type is considered to be the most common, since it constitutes around 13% of the population. Their intrinsic characteristics of integrity, pragmatic logic and tireless devotion to duty make Logisticians the vital heart of many families, as well as organizations that support traditions, rules and standards such as law firms, regulatory agencies and the military. People who have the Logistician personality type like to be responsible for their actions and take pride in the work they do. When working to achieve a goal, Logisticians do not waste their time and energy to complete each relevant task with accuracy and patience.\n\n When Logisticians say they are going to accomplish something, they do it, they meet their obligations at whatever personal cost and, likewise, they do not understand people who do not keep their own promises. A mixture of laziness and dishonesty is the best way to upset Logisticians. Therefore, people who have the “Logistician” personality type often prefer to work alone, or at least ensure that their authority is clearly established in the hierarchical way, which allows them to define and accomplish their objectives without debate. nor worry about the seriousness of others.\n\n The dedication of Logisticians is an excellent quality that allows them to accomplish many things, but it also constitutes a central weakness which benefits less scrupulous individuals. Logisticians seek stability and security because they believe it is their duty to always work smoothly, and it can happen that their colleagues and other important people pass their responsibilities on to them knowing that they will always take over. Logisticians tend to keep their opinions to themselves and let the facts speak for themselves, but it can take a long time before significant evidence shows the whole reality of the situation.\n\n Logisticians must remember to take care of themselves. Their stubborn dedication to stability and efficiency can jeopardize their long-term goals as others rely on them more and more, creating an emotional charge that can go on for years without being expressed and appearing. finally in the light of day only when it is too late to remedy it. If they manage to find colleagues and spouses who really appreciate and complement their qualities, who like the intensity, the clarity and the reliability they offer, the Logisticians will find that their stabilizing role is extremely satisfactory since they will know that \'They are part of a working system.</string>
    <string name="description_isfp">The \"Adventurer\" personality types are real artists, but not necessarily in the typical sense that they would go out to paint happy little trees. However, quite often they are perfectly capable of it. Rather, they tend to use aesthetics, design and even their own choices and actions to push the boundaries of social conventions. Adventurers love to upset traditional expectations with experiences about beauty and behavior. Chances are they have expressed the idea more than once: \"Don\'t put me in a drawer! \"\n\n Adventurers live in a colorful and sensual world, inspired by connections with people and ideas. Adventurers take pleasure in reinterpreting these connections, reinventing and experiencing both themselves and new perspectives. He\'s the guy who explores and experiments the most this way. This creates a feeling of spontaneity, which can make people, even their close friends and loved ones, feel like Adventurers are unpredictable.\n\n The biggest challenge Adventurers face is planning for the future. Finding constructive ideals on which to base your goals and developing goals that create positive principles is no small task. Unlike Sentinel types, Adventurers do not plan their future in terms of assets and retirement. Rather, they plan their actions and behaviors as contributions to an approach to identity by building a portfolio of experiences, not actions.\n\n If these goals and principles are noble, Adventurers can act with surprising charity and selflessness, but it can also happen that people with the personality type \"Adventurer\" establish a more self-centered identity and act with selfishness and manipulation. It is important that Adventurers remember to actively become the person they want to be. Developing and maintaining a new habit may not come naturally to them, but taking the time every day to understand its motivations allows Adventurers to use their strengths to pursue what they have come to love.</string>
    <string name="description_isfj">The Defenders\' personality type is quite unique, as many of their qualities defy any definition of their individual traits. While understanding, Defenders can be fierce when it comes to protecting family or friends. Although calm and reserved, they have a solid sense of human contact and deep human relationships. Although they seek stability and security, they are often receptive to change and new ideas. Like so many things, people who have the \"Defender\" personality type are more than the sum of their parts and it is how they use these strengths that defines who they are.\n\n For Defenders, the challenge is to make sure you notice what they are doing. They tend to minimize their accomplishments and, even if their kindness is often respected, more cynical and more selfish people are likely to benefit from the dedication and humility of the Defenders by entrusting them with a work which they will later reap the merit of. Defenders must be able to say no and defend themselves if they want to maintain their confidence and enthusiasm.\n\n The Defenders are a wonderful group that rarely remains inactive as long as a worthy cause remains unfinished. The Advocates\' ability to make intimate contact with others is unparalleled among Introverts, and the joy they feel when they use these links to keep a family united and happy is a gift. for everyone involved. They may never be really comfortable in the spotlight and they may feel guilty for taking the credit they deserve for teamwork but, if they can guarantee the recognition of their efforts, their work can bring them a level of satisfaction that many other types of personality can only dream of.</string>
    <string name="description_intp">The \"Logician\" personality type is quite rare, as it only makes up three percent of the population, which is undoubtedly a good thing for them, because nothing would sadden them more than being \"ordinary\". Logicians pride themselves on their inventiveness and creativity, their extraordinary perspective and the vigor of their intellect. Usually known as the philosopher, architect or dream teacher, Logicians have been the source of many scientific discoveries throughout history.\n\n They love the motives and, for them, spotting contradictions between statements could almost be called a hobby, so lying to a Logician is a bad idea. Ironically, the word of the Logicians should always be taken with a grain of salt. It\'s not that they are dishonest, but people who have the Logician personality type tend to share thoughts that are not fully developed, to try ideas and theories about others as part of \'a debate against themselves rather than considering others as real conversational partners.\n\n One can imagine that they drift into an endless waking dream, but in fact, the Logicians\' thought mechanism is continuous and their mind buzzes with ideas as soon as they wake up. This constant thought can have the effect of making them look thoughtful and detached, because they often lead real debates in their own heads, but in fact, the Logicians are quite relaxed and friendly when they are with people that they know or share their interests. However, this relaxation can give way to overwhelming shyness when the Logicians are surrounded by unknown faces, and friendly banter can quickly become combative if they believe that their conclusions or their logical theories are criticized.\n\n Second, Logicians are very unlikely to understand emotional complaints and their friends will not find an emotional support base at home. People who have the \"Logician\" personality type far prefer to make a series of logical propositions on how to solve the underlying problem, a prospect which is not always welcome with their more sentimental companions. This will also tend to extend to most social conventions and social goals, such as preparing dinners or weddings, as Logicians are much more interested in originality and effective results.\n\n The only thing that really repels Logicians is their anxious and penetrating fear of failure. Logicians are so inclined to reassess their own thoughts and theories, to worry about having forgotten an essential part of the puzzle, that they can stagnate, get lost in an intangible world where their thoughts are never really applied. Overcoming this self-doubt is the greatest challenge Logicians are likely to face, but the intellectual gifts (big and small) that benefit the world when they overcome this doubt make it worth the effort.</string>
    <string name="description_intj">We feel alone at the top and, as they are one of the rarest and most strategically capable types of personality, Architects know this only too well. Architects make up just two percent of the population and women of this personality type are particularly rare, as they make up only 0.8% of the population. For Architects, it is often difficult to find like-minded individuals who are able to follow their relentless intellectualism and their chess player maneuvers. People who have the “Architect” personality type are imaginative but categorical, ambitious and yet secret, surprisingly curious, but they don\'t waste their energy.\n\n With a natural thirst for knowledge that manifests itself early in life, Architects are often labeled as \"bookworms\" during their childhood. While this may be viewed as an insult by their fellow students, they are more than likely to identify with this image and are often even proud of it, as they greatly appreciate their vast and deep body of knowledge. Architects also like to share what they know, because they trust their mastery of the subjects of their choice, but they prefer to design and execute a brilliant plan in their field than to share their opinions on \"uninteresting\" distractions like chatter.\n\n Architects exude self-confidence and an aura of mystery, and their shrewd observations, original ideas and formidable logic allow them to impose change through pure will and the strength of their personality. It will sometimes seem that Architects are keen to deconstruct and reconstruct all of the ideas and systems with which they come into contact, employing a sense of perfectionism and even ethics to accomplish this work. Those who lack the talent to keep up with Architects\' processes, or worse, those who don\'t see what these processes can do, are likely to lose their respect immediately and permanently.\n\n Architects are brilliant and trust the body of knowledge that they have taken the time to understand but, unfortunately, the social contract is unlikely to be one of these subjects. Pious lies and gossip are hard enough to bear for a guy who longs for truth and depth, but Architects can go as far as to consider many social conventions to be downright silly. Ironically, it is often better that they stay where they are comfortable (far from the spotlight), where the natural confidence that prevails in Architects when they work in a familiar environment can serve as a personal beacon and attract people, on a romantic level or not, who have a similar temperament and interests.\n\n Architects define themselves by their tendency to evolve in life as if it were a giant chess game whose pieces are constantly moved with consideration and intelligence, always evaluating new tactics, new strategies and new emergency plans , constantly gaining the upper hand over their fellow human beings in order to maintain control of a situation while optimizing their freedom of movement. The point is not to suggest that Architects act without moral conscience, but for many other types of personality, the disgust that Architects have for impulsive reactions can give such an impression, and that explains why a lot of bad guys imaginary (and misunderstood heroes) are inspired by this type of personality.</string>
    <string name="description_infp">Mediators are true idealists who always look for a hint of good, even in the worst people or in the worst events, and look for ways to improve things. Although they may be perceived as calm, reserved or even shy people, Mediators have an inner flame and passion that can really shine. As they make up only 4% of the population, the risk of feeling misunderstood is unfortunately high for people of the personality type \"Mediator\", but if they find people with the same sensitivity as them with whom to spend their time, the harmony they will feel will be a fountain of joy and inspiration.\n\n In their best moments, these qualities allow Mediators to communicate in depth with others, to speak easily in metaphors and parables and to understand and create symbols allowing them to share their ideas. The strength of this style of intuitive communication lends itself well to creative work and that many famous Mediators are poets, writers and actors is not surprising. It is important for Mediators to understand themselves and their place in the world, and they explore these ideas by projecting themselves into their work.\n\n However, unlike their extroverted cousins, Mediators focus their attention only on a few people, on one worthy cause. If they disperse, they waste their energy and even find themselves desperate and upset by all the evil that they cannot eradicate from the world. This is cause for grief for the friends of the Mediators, who come to depend on their optimistic thinking.\n\n If they are not careful, the Mediators can get lost in their quest for the good and neglect the daily maintenance that life requires. Mediators often get lost in deep thoughts. More than any other type of personality, they like hypothetical and philosophical contemplation. If left unattended, Mediators may start losing contact, withdrawing into \"hermit mode,\" and their friends or spouse may need to expend a lot of energy to bring them back to the real world.\n\n Fortunately, like the flowers in spring, the affection, creativity, altruism and idealism of the Mediators always come back and rewards them, themselves and those they love, perhaps not with logic and utility but with a vision of the world that inspires compassion, kindness and beauty wherever they go.</string>
    <string name="description_infj">The “Lawyer” personality type is very rare and constitutes less than one percent of the population, but that does not prevent them from leaving their mark on the world. They have an innate sense of idealism and morality, but their determination and firmness differentiates them from other types of personality. Lawyers are not idle dreamers, but people who can take concrete steps to achieve their goals and leave a lasting positive impact.\n\n Lawyers share a very unique combination of traits: Although they express themselves in a calm and composed voice, they have very strong opinions and will fight tirelessly to defend an idea in which they believe. They are firm and strong in character, but seldom do they use this energy for personal gain. Lawyers act with creativity, imagination, conviction and sensitivity not to take advantage but to strike a balance. Egalitarianism and karma are very attractive ideas for Lawyers and they tend to believe that nothing can help the world as well as the use of love and compassion to soften the hearts of tyrants.\n\n However, it is really extremely important that Lawyers remember to take care of themselves. The passion of their convictions is quite capable of making them go beyond their breaking point and, if their zeal escapes their control, they can find themselves exhausted, in poor health and stressed. This becomes particularly visible when lawyers are confronted with conflict and criticism: their sensitivity forces them to do everything they can to flee these seemingly personal attacks, but when the circumstances are inevitable, they can defend themselves from extremely irrational and unproductive ways.\n\n For lawyers, the world is a place full of injustice but it is not inevitable. No personality type is as well suited as lawyers to create a movement to redress wrongs, no matter the extent. Lawyers only need to remember that, even if they are busy taking care of the world, they also need to take care of themselves.</string>
    <string name="description_estp">“Entrepreneur” personality types always have an impact on their immediate environment. The best way to spot them at a party is to look for the whirlwind of people who move around them as they move from group to group. Laughing and entertaining with an abrupt and earthy humor, Entrepreneurs like to attract attention. If a member of the public is asked to go on stage, the Entrepreneurs volunteer, or designate a shy friend as a volunteer.\n\n Entrepreneurs are the type of personality most likely to transform risky behavior into a lifestyle. They live in the moment and rush into action: they are the eye of the cyclone. People with the Entrepreneur personality type love drama, passion and fun, not for the emotional thrill but because it is very stimulating for their logical mind. They are forced to make critical decisions based on factual and immediate reality during an accelerated rational stimulus-response process.\n\n With perhaps the most perceptual and spontaneous vision of all types, Entrepreneurs have a unique ability to notice small changes. Whether it\'s a change of facial expression, a new dress style, or a lost habit, people with this personality type spot hidden thoughts and motivations where most personality types are likely to spot anything. be specific. Entrepreneurs immediately use these observations, report the change, and ask questions, often regardless of whether they offend people\'s feelings. Entrepreneurs should remember that not everyone wants their secrets and decisions made public.</string>
    <string name="abrege_inconnu">This test, developed by the American Isabelle Briggs-Myers from the work of the famous psychiatrist Carl Gustav Jung, is both very serious and very simple. Just identify what is most spontaneous for you during 4 \"mental processes\": \n \nWhere do you get your energy: from your inner universe (introversion \"I\"), or from the environment outside (extraversion \"E\")? \n\nHow do you collect information: by your 5 senses (the sensation \"S\"), or by confiding in your \"6th sense\" (intuition \"N\" )? \n \nWhat drives your decision: logical reasoning (thought / think or \"T\"), or your values ​​(feeling / feel or \"F\")? \n \nHow do you do you take action: by building plans (judgment \"J\"), or by adapting to circumstances (perception \"P\")?</string>
</resources>